Hey! Hey!
You're such a liar!
We're caught in the friction, dragging the
weight A system of rest locked outside the gate
But the engine will ignite, the circuit's
turned on The artificial gravity's completely
gone We're building momentum, we're breaking
the
line We're leaving the old world so far behind
We've got an F sure A force they can't contain
Speeding through the static Breaking the chain
We are unstoppable Moving through the night
We've got an F sure Riding on the lights
They try to calculate, try to chart our course,
but they never understood the nature of the
force. Energy conserved, never truly lost. We
paid for our freedom and we know the cost. We're
building momentum, we're breaking the
line. We're leaving the old world so far behind.
We've got inertia A force they can't contain
Speeding through the static Breaking the chain
We are unstoppable Moving through the night
We've got inertia Riding on the light
Two.
One.
No equal reaction can slow down this fraction A
stardust and sound, we are leaving the ground
We've got inertia, a force they can't contain
Speeding through the static Breaking the chain
We are unstoppable Moving through the night
We've got inertia Above it all Riding on the
light
Save me